(phone rings)
하워드입니다
Howard Wolowitz.
데이브 로거야
MAN: Hey, Howard.
Dave Roeger here at NASA.
NASA 임무 관련 얘기 하려고
We need to talk
about your upcoming mission.
네, 푸시업 열심히
하고 있어요
Yes, yes, I've been doing
my push-ups.
아직 9개밖에 못 하지만
I'm still stuck at nine, but...
도움 없이 정자세로 가능합니다
...that's going all the way down
with no one holding me.
잘했네,
할 말이 있어서 연락했어
That's great, uh,
but that's not why I called.
뭔가 기술적인 문제가 생겼어
We've run into a bit of a snafu.
소유즈 캡슐이
가압테스트를 통과 못했서
Your Soyuz capsule failed
the pressurization test,
비행 취소다
so bottom line,
mission's been scrubbed.
그럼 어떻게 되는거죠?
You're kidding.
So what does that mean?
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. (laughs)
뭐라 해야할지
Boy, I got to tell you,
정말 실망이네요
I'm really disappointed.
어릴 때부터
꿈꿔왔던 일인데
This was my dream
ever since I was a little kid.
네
Okay, well, uh,
연락주셔서 감사해요
thanks for the call.
Yep, you, too.
Yes! Thank you!
(laughs):
Oh! Oh...
우주에서 죽을 일은 없겠네
I'm not gonna die in space!
(chuckling)
신이 계획한 대로
죽을 거야
(exhales) I'm gonna die
the way God intended,
심장에 지방이 쌓여서
50대 후반에 가겠지
in my late 50s,
with a heart full of pastrami.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x23
The Launch Acceleration
Original Air Date on May 3, 2012
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
셔츠가 좀 더 커야겠어
SHELDON: I'm going to need
a larger shirt.
겨드랑이가 너무 낀다
This one's a little tight
under the arms.
Okay.
내복을 입어서
끼는 건 아니고?
Do you think maybe it's tight
because you're wearing
long underwear?
그래서 끼는 거 맞아
Yes, of course
that's why it's tight.
질문을 다시할게
All right, let me
rephrase the question.
내복은 왜 입었어?
Why are you wearing
long underwear?
제대로 물어본 거야?
You're kidding.
넌 왜 안 입었는데?
Shouldn't the question be:
why aren't you?
제대로 물어봤거든
No, it should be: why are you?
(sighs) Leonard,
대여용 턱시도는 낯선
사람들의 땀내에 쩔어있어
these rental tuxedos have been
worn by hundreds
of sweaty strangers.
내 땀도 건드리고
싶지 않은데
I don't like my own sweat
touching my skin,
남의 땀은 더하지
how do you think
I feel about theirs?
이거로 입어보세요
Why don't you
slip this on?
사형수한테 올가미를
건네주는 것과 같네요
Said the hangman
offering a noose.
볼링화 대여할
때만큼은 아니지만
Well, that wasn't
as entertaining
as when he rents bowling shoes,
이번에도 볼만하네
but it was right up there.
끝났네
Well, that's it.
계획이 취소됐어
My orders have been rescinded.
정식으로 폐지됐다
I am officially "no go"
to space.
안됐다
I'm sorry, Howard,
but I got to tell you,
이제 마음이 한결 가볍긴 하다
I'm a little relieved
you're not going.
왜?
Why?
러시아에서 60년대에
설계한 로켓이였잖아
Come on, you were
gonna go up in a rocket
designed in the 1960s
by the Russians.
그런데?
Yeah, so?
전자제품 살 때도
보면 알잖아
When was the last time
you were at Best Buy
러시아산 블루레이
플레이어라고 광고하지 않아
and you heard someone say, "Ooh,
check out this Blu-ray player,
it must be good,
it was built in Russia"?
기술력이 그렇게
떨어지지 않아
Well, their technology
isn't that bad.
소유즈 캡슐을 타고 오면
When you come back to Earth
in a Soyuz capsule, you free-fall
시속 800km로
자유낙하하게 돼
from space
at 500 miles per hour,
유일하게 속도를
늦춰주는 건
and the only thing
that slows you down
땅에 닿기 직전에
펼쳐지는 작은 낙하산이야
is a little parachute
that pops out
right before you crash
into the ground.
록키와 불윙클도 못 잡은
놈들이 디자인한 거라고
And the whole thing
was designed
by the same brilliant minds
who were unable to capture
Rocky and Bullwinkle.
All right, well, whatever.
난 그런 걱정 안 했어
I wasn't worried.
그래?
You weren't?
우리가 어떻게
다른지 설명해줄게
Let me explain the difference
between you and me.
넌 스타트렉을 보기만 하고,
난 그렇게 살거든
(sighs)
You watch
Star Trek; I live it.
비행 취소 후 턱시도 가게에서
자랑하는 에피소드는 없던데
Oh, please. I don't remember
the episode of Star Trek
where the guy
never goes to space
and brags about it
in a tuxedo store.
우스갯소리로 넘겨도 좋아
Make all the jokes you want,
어쨌든 내가 할뻔 했다는
사실은 변하지 않아
but there's only
one of us here brave enough
to almost do
what I almost did.
훨씬 낫네
SHELDON:
Ah, much better.
덥겠다
You must be burning up.
너네 요도보다는 덜 뜨거울걸
A little. But not more
than your urethras
바지에 묻은 세균이 침입하면
will be after whatever's
in those pants swims up them.
Well...
근사하면서 위생적이지?
I cut quite the dashing,
yet hygienic figure, don't I?
결혼을 앞둔 플래시 같아
I look like the Flash
about to get married.
티슈다!
Oh! A tissue! A tissue!
Oh, good Lord!
어디 가신거죠?
Uh, where's he going?
차에 비상 세정제를 두거든요
He keeps emergency
Purell in the car.
열쇠!
Keys! Keys! Keys!
- 안녕
- 미리 말해야할 것 같아서
Hey, you.
Before I come in,
나한테 가스가 있어
you should know, I have gas.
네가 한 멘트 중에
최악은 아니였어
For the record,
not your worst opening line.
자유전자 레이저에서 고전압을
발생시킬 때 사용되는 가스야
Check it out.
It's the gas I use
in my free-electron laser
to support high voltages.
다른 용도고 있어
But it also has an
interesting secondary use.
(gas hissing)
들이마셔봐
Here. Breathe this in.
경찰 아닌 거 맞지?
B-Before I do it, if you're
a cop you have tell me, right?
해봐
Just try it.
Okay.
(inhales)
마시면 어떻게...
(very deep voice):
What's it supposed to...
세상에
Oh, my God, that's so freaky!
(laughs)
(inhales)
넌 못된 놈이야, 그린치
(very deep voice):
♪ You're a mean one ♪
♪ Mr. Grinch. ♪
(laughs)
나도, 나도
Okay. Me, me, me. Ready?
레너드, 내가 니 애비다
(very deep voice):
Leonard, I am your father.
(both laughing)
남자 목소리를 내는 여자한테
I have never been
more attracted to a woman
이렇게 끌린 적은 처음이야
who sounds like a man
in my life.
Oh... (laughs)
Mm.
있잖아
Hey... you know
how we've been...
진도를 천천히 하기로 했었지?
taking things slow?
Mm-hmm.
생각을 해보니
Well, I've been thinking, and...
준비된 거 같아
maybe I'm ready to...
속도를 내도 돼
take things a little... faster.
Oh...
좋아
great.
Mm-hmm.
4달이나 기다렸잖아,
속도는 걱정하지 마
And I promise,
after waiting four months,
fast is what you're gonna get.
하나만 더
You know, just-just one thing.
지금 사이가 딱 좋아
Look, we're in a really
great place right now,
뭔가 실수를 해서
어색한 사이가 되진 말자
and I don't want to do anything
that will make stuff
all weird again.
그런 일 없을거야
So we won't let it get weird.
미리 말하는 건데
Okay. Oh, and just a heads-up...
지난 번 이후
mm, since the last time
you saw me naked,
쿠키몬스터 문신을 했어
I got a Cookie Monster tattoo.
적절한 반응을 보여
The acceptable responses
when you see it
좋은 말 아니면 가만히 있어
are "awesome" or nothing.
이건 어때?
What about...
쿠키!
(very deep voice):
Cookies!
(laughs)
(balloon sputters)
에이미?
(knocking)
SHELDON: Amy?
Amy?
(knocking)
7시 딱 맞춰왔네
7:00, right on time.
우연이 아냐
It's not an accident.
20분 동안 밖에서 기다렸어
I waited outside your door
for 20 minutes.
저녁 거의 다 됐어
Well, dinner's almost ready.
I must say,
데이트를 너네 집에서
하자고 해서 의외였어
I was surprised
you chose to spend
our date night
in your apartment.
As I mentioned,
시의회에서 신호등 녹색 불
시간 늘리기를 토론한대
the Pasadena City Council is
debating longer crosswalk times,
레고 매장은 세일 중이고
and later, the LEGO store is
having a midnight madness sale.
누구나 가고 싶은 데이트야
You ask anyone,
that's a hot date.
솔긴하긴 하지만
오늘은 특별한걸 준비했어
Tempting choices,
but I have something special
planned for tonight.
인디아나 존스 레고를 향해
What can be more special
than having
여유롭게 횡단보도를
건널 수 있는데
an adequate amount of time
to cross the street
이보다 더 특별한게 있을까?
on your way to buy
a tiny LEGO Indiana Jones?
친구들의 관계 발전을 지켜보며
With our friends moving forward
in their relationships,
우리도 발전하면
좋겠다고 생각했어
I've decided that we should
make progress in ours as well.
Oh, dear Lord.
2년 전에는
모르는 사이였어
Two years ago,
we didn't even know each other,
지금은 해가 떨어졌는데
너네 집에 놀러왔고
and now I'm
in your apartment after dark.
얼마나 더 발전하려고?
How much faster
can this thing go?
이렇게 나올 줄 알았지
I had a feeling
you'd be reluctant,
신경 생물학적 기법을
활용하기로 했어
which is why
I'm going to dip
into my neurobiological
bag of tricks.
아이고, 맘대로 하셔
(laughs): Oh, you brain monkeys
kill me. Dip away.
단기간에 나에 대한 감정을
증폭시킬 실험을 준비했어
I have devised
an experiment that
I believe will increase
your feelings for me
in an accelerated time frame.
어떻게?
And how do you propose
to do that?
마약을 이용한
사고 통제는 아니지?
Uh, hope you're not thinking
about some sort
of LSD thought control.
내 사고를 넓히는
마약은 이미 있어
Because there's
only one mind-expanding drug
that this man enjoys,
학교라고 들어봤나?
and that's called school.
인간은 자라면서
감정적인 애착이 생기지
Human beings form emotional
attachments as they grow up.
네 대상은 엄마나
슈퍼히어로였지
In your case, to your mother,
superheroes, et cetera.
그런 감정을 나한테
옮기는 실험을 할거야
I'm going to attempt
an experiment that will
get you to transfer
those feelings to me.
Well,
오늘 메뉴는 허튼수작에
사이드로 헛소리군
seems what's on the menu tonight
is malarkey with
a big side of poppycock.
두고 보자
We'll see.
로맨틱한 배경 음악을 깔자
Let's start with a little
romantic dinner music, shall we?
(Super Mario Bros.
video game music playing)
슈퍼 마리오?
Super Mario Bros. theme?
응
Yes.
무슨 작전인지 알겠다
I see what you're doing.
에빙하우스의 기억실험이네
You're attempting
to build on the work
of Ebbinghaus by triggering
어린 시절의 추억을
떠올리게 하려고
an involuntary memory
of me playing that game--
가장 행복했던
600시간이긴 하지만
admittedly the happiest
600 hours of my childhood...
효과 없을거야
...but it won't work.
즐거운 식사를 하자,
여기 앉아
Fine. There's no reason
we still can't have
a lovely dinner.
Why don't you have a seat.
(Sheldon humming along
with song)
Boink! Boink!
마실거 줄까?
May I offer you
something to drink?
안 마시는거 알잖아
You know I don't drink.
딸기맛 네스퀵인데?
Not even...
strawberry Quik?
(quiet gasp)
딸기맛 네스퀵은 좋아해
I love strawberry Quik.
내가 제일 좋아하는
핑크색 유체야
It's my favorite
pink fluid,
2번째는 펩토 비스몰이지
narrowly beating out
Pepto-Bismol.
알아
Oh, I know.
저녁 메뉴랑
잘 어울릴 거야
I think it will go nicely
with what I have prepared...
for dinner.
소시지 스파게티네
(gasps) Spaghetti with little pieces
of hot dog cut up in it!
너네 엄마표 스파게티야
Just like your mommy
used to make.
Oh...
yummy, yummy!
너랑 더 자주 만나고 싶어
We should do this more often.
Uh-oh.
미안해
LEONARD:
I'm sorry. I did,
내가 도를 지나쳤네
I crossed a line.
I didn't mean to!
섹스 도중에 어떻게
그런 말을 할 수 있어?
Who says something
like that right in the middle
of sex?!
I don't know,
그냥 튀어 나왔어
it just came out.
People say weird things
섹스할 때 이상한
말 많이 하잖아
during sex all the time.
아무도 그런 말은
하지 않을거야
Okay, well, they
sure as hell don't say that.
너무 뜨거운 순간이어서
It was the heat of the moment.
No,
'그래, 바로 그렇게'가 아니라?
the heat of the moment is,
"Ooh, yeah, just like that,"
'나랑 결혼해줄래?'
not "will you marry me?"
미안해
I'm sorry.
한번만 기회를 줘
Just-just give me
another chance.
이불 속에서 속삭이려고?
Why, so you can crawl
under the covers and go,
교육 환경이 좋은
동네를 알아볼자고 하려고?
"Hey, baby,
want to go look for houses
in neighborhoods
with good schools?"
진자 미안해
Again, I'm sorry.
하워드랑 베르나데트가
곧 결혼하잖아
You know, with Howard
and Bernadette getting married,
나도 분위기에 휩싸여서
I got caught up
in a little wedding fever.
아까 한 말은 취소할게
I take it back.
You can't
쉽게 잊혀지는 말이 아냐
take something like that back.
이젠 어떡할 거야?
I mean, what are we
even supposed to do now?
나중에 돌아보면
재밌는 에피소드일 뿐이야
Okay, at some point,
we'll look back
and this is going
to be a funny story.
지금부터 그렇게 생각하자
Why don't we just
start doing that now?
- 장난해?
- 아니
You're kidding.
No.
그때 기억나?
Hey, do you remember...
침대에서 내가
프로포즈 했을 때
...that time when I proposed
to you in bed?
(laughs)
넌 기겁했잖아
And you were all, like,
"What are you doing?"
(laughs)
재밌지
That was so funny.
완전 재밌지
So funny.
재미없어
It's not funny.
좀 기다려봐
Give it a minute.
미소 짓고 있는 거 아닌가?
Is that a little smile
I see there?
가야겠다
I should go.
생각해봤는데
Hey, I was thinking.
결혼식 때 '더티 댄싱'
춤을 따라하면 어떨까?
For our first dance
at the wedding,
what if we learn the final number
from Dirty Dancing?
- 진짜?
- 한번 해보자
You're kidding.
No,
come on.
멋질 거 같아
How cool would that be?
내가 너한테 안기면
Me running
into your arms...
넌 날 들어올리고
you lifting me up
into the air.
기분이 좋아 보여
Oh, you're in a good mood.
당연히 기분 좋지
Yeah, well, why
wouldn't I be?
내 이상형이랑 결혼하게 됐고
You know, I'm marrying
the girl of my dreams,
엄마는 허니문에
빠지기로 하셨어
and I finally got
my mother to agree
not to come on
our honeymoon.
잠시만
(phone rings)
Oh, hang on.
NASA야
Oh, it's NASA.
왈로위츠입니다
Wolowitz.
데이브, 무슨 일인가요?
Oh! Hi, Dave.
What's up?
정말요?
No kidding. Really?
Well,
잘됐네요
that's... great news.
Great, great news.
네, 이메일 확인할게요
All right, I'll watch my e-mail
for the details.
다음에 봐요
Okay, talk soon.
좋은 일 있어?
What's so great?
비행을 하게 될 거 같아
It looks like I'm going
into space after all.
(nervous chuckle)
하위, 너무 잘됐다
Oh, Howie,
that's wonderful!
그래, 그렇지
Uh-huh, wonderful.
(shakily):
Yay...
취소된 거 아니였어?
What happened?
I thought
they canceled your mission.
Th-They did.
우주 정거장에
망원경을 설치하고 싶대
But NASA really wants
my telescope up
on the space station,
더 일찍 떠나게 됐어
so they're putting me
on an earlier launch.
언제?
When?
A...
다음 주 금요일
week from Friday.
다음 주 일요일이 결혼식인데
What? We're getting
married that Sunday.
그러네
You're right!
못 가겠다
I-I can't go to space.
결혼해야 되니
못 간다고 해야지
I have to get married,
and no one can say
that's not a good reason.
I'll call him back.
네 앞길을 가로막는
여자가 되고 싶지 않아
Wait. I don't want to be
the one who stands
in your way.
어쩔 수 없어,
이미 결정된 일이야
Well, too bad, you already did.
It's a done deal.
용서할게
Oh, well.
But I forgive you.
이런 식으로
결혼하기 싫어
No. That's not how I want
to start our marriage,
네 꿈을 망치는 거잖아
killing your dream?
결혼식은 돌아올 때까지 미루자
We'll have the wedding
when you get back.
초대장도 다 보냈는데?
But wh-what about
all the plans
and the guests?
전화 돌리면 되지
We'll call them.
예약금을 이미 내서
아빠가 좋아하진 않겠지만
Although my dad's
gonna go a little nutso
over losing his deposits.
그러네
You're right, he is!
아버님께서 싫어할게 뻔해
Your dad's gonna be furious.
허락하시지 않을걸
(chuckling): There's no way he's
gonna let us postpone this wedding.
어쩔 수 없다
Well, we tried.
내가 설득해볼게
I'll talk to him.
내가 부탁하면 될 거야
He won't say no to his little girl.
No!
내가 얘기할게
I-I should talk to him,
남자 대 남자로
man to man.
(sighs)
하위, 우리 아빠는
그렇게 쉬운 분이 아냐
But, Howie, my dad
can be a bully.
결국에는 비행
취소하게 만들걸
He's gonna make you cancel
your space flight.
그러기를 바래야지
(chuckles)
We can only hope...
그러지 않기를
that he doesn't.
비숍을 4번째 칸 퀸으로
Bishop to queen four,
2층
level two.
체크
Check.
쉘든
Sheldon...
기사가 비숍 먹잖아
knight takes bishop.
괜찮아?
You all right?
응
I'm fine.
정말?
Are you?
퀸을 지키지 않고
You left your queen
exposed from above,
기사는 한 구석에 갇혔어
you trapped your
knight in the corner,
계속 한숨 쉬면서
'왜 내가'라고 하잖아
and you keep sighing
and saying, "Why me?"
(sighs)
그래
Very well.
여자에 대해
질문해도 될까?
Can I ask you
a question about women?
작년에 사준 책 있잖아
We got you that book last year.
책에 다 설명된 거 아냐?
Wasn't everything in there?
에이미랑 문제가 있어
No, I'm having
a relationship problem with Amy.
참고로
And by the way,
그 책 때문에
악몽을 꿨어
that book gave me nightmares.
위로가 될지 모르지만
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
나도 페니한테 실수했어
I screwed things up
pretty good with Penny.
우리 좀 봐, 레너드
Look at us,
Leonard...
여자 문제로 불평하는
평범한 남자들 같아
engaging in the social
convention of men bellyaching
about their ol' ladies.
그러네
I guess we are.
무슨 일인데 그래?
So, what's going on?
믿기 어렵겠지만
Believe it or not,
에이미는 내 관심을 끌려고
행복하게 만들어주고 있어
Amy has embarked on a campaign
to increase my feelings
for her by making me happy.
저런, 너무 힘들겠구나
I'm sorry, that must be very
difficult for you.
끔찍해
It's awful.
주니어 열차 기관사를
해볼 기회도 있었어
This morning,
she arranged for me
to be an Amtrak junior conductor
for the day.
보통 아이들 대상인데
It-It's usually
only open to children.
에이미가 잘 얘기했나봐
She got them
to make an exception.
부끄러운 줄 알아야지
Shame on her.
휘슬도 울리게 해줬어
They let me
blow the whistle, Leonard.
대단하네
She's good.
알아
I know.
더 있어
And it gets worse.
에이미의 노력 덕분에
Her efforts are causing me
적절하지 않은 순간에
애정을 느끼고 있어
to have affectionate
feelings for her
at inappropriate times.
침대나 샤워실에서?
You mean, like in bed
or in the shower?
아니
No!
그 악마의 책은 잊으라고
Would you please stop
referencing that infernal book?
오늘 아침을 예로 들게
For example, this morning,
진공 속 가상 입자의
무작위 운동을 계산하다가
I was calculating
the random motion
of virtual particles
in a vacuum,
입자들이 에이미의
비듬으로 변형되고
when suddenly
the particles morphed
into an image
of Amy's dandruff...
그녀의 살짝 굽은 어깨로
내려앉는 것처럼 보였어
...gently cascading down
onto her pale,
slightly hunched shoulders.
(groans)
저 여우가 나한테
무슨 짓을 한 거지?
What has that vixen
done to me, Leonard?
어떻게 멈추는 거야?
And how do I make it stop?
육체적인 관계를
거부하지 않았다면
Well, if you had
a physical relationship,
섹스를 제안했을 텐데
I'd say propose during sex.
내가 해보니
역효과가 날 수도 있더라
Turns out that's
a real mood killer.
이제 네 얘기하는 건가?
I assume we're talking
about you now?
응
Yeah.
이렇게 진행하는 거야?
So, that's
how this works?
내가 불평한 다음에
네가 불평하고
I complain,
and then you complain,
해결책은 없지?
and no one offers any solutions?
응, 대충 그래
Pretty much.
그러니까 여자들한테 잡혀살지
Well, no wonder
the women are winning.
(knock)
아버님, 시간 괜찮으세요?
Mr. Rostenkowski,
are you busy?
그냥 사진첩 보고 있어,
들어오렴
Oh, just looking at some
old pictures. Come on in.
가족 사진인가요?
Family pictures,
or...?
시체였군요
H-Holy crap, that's
a dead person.
퇴직하기 전에 맡았던
살인 사건이야
Last murder case
before I retired.
시체가 몇 구나 보이냐?
How many bodies
do you see there?
잘 생각해
Careful,
단순한 질문이 아냐
it's a trick question.
잘 모르겠어요
I'm not sure.
됐어, 넌 절대 못 맞춰
Nah, you'll never get it.
정수가 아니거든
It's a fraction.
그렇군요
How about that.
Anyway,
할 말이 있어서 왔어요
sir, I need to talk
to you about something.
(cracking)
호두 먹을래?
Walnut?
아뇨, 괜찮습니다
No, thank you.
알레르기가 있어서요
I'm allergic.
Oh, sure.
내 파트너도 그랬었지
My partner used to have that.
지금은 죽었지만
He's dead now.
견과류 때문에요?
From nuts?
아니, 아내가 쏴 죽였어
Nah, his wife shot him.
정신 나간 여자였지
But she was nuts,
so in a way...
재밌는 일화네요
Nice story.
Anyway,
할 말이 있는데요
the reason I wanted
to talk to you is
NASA에서 비행
스케줄을 앞당겼어요
NASA has moved up
my launch
to the International
Space Station.
그런데?
Yeah, so?
So...
결혼식 날짜랑 겹쳐서요
the date is going
to conflict
with me marrying
your daughter.
무슨 말씀 하실지 알겠어요
Now, I know what you're
going to say-- I made
베르나데트한테
약속을 했는데
a commitment to Bernadette
and to your family
결혼식을 미루는 건
말이 안되죠
and I've got a hell
of a lot of nerve
coming in here and demanding
that we postpone this thing.
네, 잘 알아들었어요
Well, message heard
and understood.
비행 취소할게요,
감사합니다
Mission canceled.
Thank you.
어디 가는데?
Where are you going?
죄송합니다
I'm sorry.
나가봐도 될까요?
May I be excused?
아니
No, you may not.
나도 할 말이 있다네
Let me tell you something.
자네를 처음 봤을 때
When I first met you...
계속 서 있으려고?
You just gonna stand there?
죄송해요
I'm sorry, I didn't know,
is this going to...
그럼 앉을까요
Well, I should sit...
앉아도 될까요?
그냥 앉을게요
May I be seat...
Well, I'll just sit.
자네를 처음 봤을 때
When I first met you,
마음에 들지 않았어
I didn't like you.
알고 있습니다
I'm aware of that, sir.
그러다 같이
시간을 보냈지
But then you and I
had some time together.
Uh-huh.
나아지지 않았지
It did not get better.
네, 네
Right, right.
비틀지 머리 스타일에
That silly Beatle haircut
and...
빨간 스쿠터를 타고 다니고
you riding around
on a red Vespa,
그 나이에 아직도
엄마랑 같이 살다니
and you're still living
at home with your mother.
우리 딸이 나한테
벌 주는 줄 알았어
To be honest, I thought
Bernadette chose you
to punish me.
그러다 우주비행사
얘기를 들었고
But then I heard about
your astronaut thing,
내가 너무 섣부르게
판단한게 아닌가 싶었지
and I realized
I judged you too fast.
자네한테 우리 딸을
맡겨도 될 것 같았다네
Maybe you are
the right guy
for my little girl.
참고로 말씀드리면
Oh, I am.
And just so you know,
비행을 하지 않아도
우주비행사 신분은 유지돼요
I'd still be an astronaut,
even if I didn't go to space.
ID 카드랑
NASA 골프 셔츠도 있어요
I've got an I.D. card
and a NASA golf shirt.
아니, 비행은 가야지
No, no, you got to go.
이런 기회를 놓치면 안돼
You can't turn down
an opportunity like this.
결혼식이랑 예약금은
어떡하고요?
B-But what about the wedding
and all the money you put
down for the reception?
그런 건 내가 처리할게
You let me worry about that.
마음 놓고
임무를 수행하고 오게
You go up to that
space station,
그래야 자랑스러운 사위지
and you make me proud.
네
Um, okay.
(laughs)
문제 있나?
You got a problem with that?
솔직히 말씀드릴게요
All right, look, I'm
gonna level with you.
비행이 너무 두려워요
I'm terrified about
going into space.
못 돌아오면 어쩌죠?
What if I don't
make it back?
잘 될 거야
It's gonna be okay, son.
정말 그렇게 생각하세요?
You really think so?
물론이지
Of course.
베르나데트처럼
이쁜 아이는
A pretty girl like Bernadette...
새로운 남자가 생길 거야
she'll find a new guy.
Hey.
출근해?
Off to work?
응
Yeah.
좋은 밤 보내
Have a nice night.
너도
Okay, you, too.
페니, 잠깐
Penny, just, wait.
지난 번 침대에서
한 말 있잖아
I've been thinking
about what I said
when we were in bed
the other night.
응, 나도 생각 많이 했어
Yeah, I've been
thinking about it, too.
대답을 못 받았더라고
I noticed you never answered me.
그러네
You're right.
싫어
No.
아직 연애 중인가?
Uh, follow-up.
Are we still dating?
응
PENNY:
Yep.
프로포즈 때문에
아직 어색해?
Is it still weird
'cause I proposed?
응
Yep.
질문이 몇 개 더 있어
I have a couple more
quick questions.
차에서 전화해줄래?
Do you want to call me
from the car?
아니
No!
잘 해낸 것 같네
Think I played that
pretty well.
(electronic whirring)
(electronic whirring continues)
(whirring stops)
안녕, 레너드
Hello, Leonard.
뭐해?
What are you doing?
의사 놀이
We're playing doctor.
스타트렉 스타일로
Star Trek style.
난 지옥에 있어
I'm in hell, Leonard.
계속해
Don't stop.
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==